<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<java version="1.7.0_10" class="java.beans.XMLDecoder">
 <object class="com.results.YoutubeResult">
  <void property="displaySummary">
   <string>India and China: Can two tigers share a mountain? Lecture at The Australian National University by David M Malone, 20 April 2010.To outsiders, India and China show some striking similarities. Both are ancient civilizations reincarnated as modern republics in the mid twentieth century, and are now rising powers. Both have nuclear weapons, burgeoning economies, expanding military budgets and large reservoirs of manpower, and seem to be vying for influence in the Indian Ocean, the Persian Gulf, Africa, Central Asia and East Asia. Yet little attention is paid to the relationships between them.(From India and China: Conflict and Cooperation by David M Malone and Rohan Mukherjee, Survival, 2010)David M Malone is the President of the Canadian International Development Research Centre. Mr. Malone served as Canadas High Commissioner to India and non-resident Ambassador to Bhutan and Nepal. Other positions he has held include: Assistant Deputy Minister (Global Issues) in Canadas Department of Foreign Affairs and International Trade; President, International Peace Academy, New York; and as a Canadian Ambassador to the United Nations in New York. Mr. Malone has published extensively on peace and security issues. He has taught at Columbia University and the University of Toronto. He currently serves as Adjunct Professor at the New York University School of Law and is a Senior Fellow of Massey College in the University of Toronto. His most recent book is The Law and Practice of the United Nations (OUP, 2008). He is completing work on a book addressing contemporary Indian foreign policy, Does the Elephant Dance?, to be published by OUP in 2011. viewcount:0 Time:null</string>
  </void>
  <void property="docID">
   <string>b273d4a3-e613-4f51-96da-e3b5f65d10a5</string>
  </void>
  <void property="link">
   <string>http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=pOlWZAzTTHI</string>
  </void>
  <void property="source">
   <int>4</int>
  </void>
  <void property="summary">
   <string>India and China: Can two tigers share a mountain? Lecture at The Australian National University by David M Malone, 20 April 2010.To outsiders, India and China show some striking similarities. Both are ancient civilizations reincarnated as modern republics in the mid twentieth century, and are now rising powers. Both have nuclear weapons, burgeoning economies, expanding military budgets and large reservoirs of manpower, and seem to be vying for influence in the Indian Ocean, the Persian Gulf, Africa, Central Asia and East Asia. Yet little attention is paid to the relationships between them.(From India and China: Conflict and Cooperation by David M Malone and Rohan Mukherjee, Survival, 2010)David M Malone is the President of the Canadian International Development Research Centre. Mr. Malone served as Canadas High Commissioner to India and non-resident Ambassador to Bhutan and Nepal. Other positions he has held include: Assistant Deputy Minister (Global Issues) in Canadas Department of Foreign Affairs and International Trade; President, International Peace Academy, New York; and as a Canadian Ambassador to the United Nations in New York. Mr. Malone has published extensively on peace and security issues. He has taught at Columbia University and the University of Toronto. He currently serves as Adjunct Professor at the New York University School of Law and is a Senior Fellow of Massey College in the University of Toronto. His most recent book is The Law and Practice of the United Nations (OUP, 2008). He is completing work on a book addressing contemporary Indian foreign policy, Does the Elephant Dance?, to be published by OUP in 2011.</string>
  </void>
  <void property="title">
   <string>India and China - David M Malone at ANU, 20 April 2010</string>
  </void>
 </object>
</java>
